If you're an amateur hairstylist and you're looking to find a way how to clean off that nasty product off your curling iron, well I'm a professional so let's take it from me.
I'm Laura Gibson, beauty expert and I'm here to give you a few tips on how to clean your curling iron.
There is always the easiest way which is after each use, you want to wait for it to cool down, because it's hot and you don't want to burn yourself.
As a stylist I can't tell you how many times I've actually burned myself, because I don't thing before I do.
So you just want to take it, wipe it down regularly.
But then there's some of us who get a little bit lazy and don't always wipe it down.
So we're going to go to our second part of how we would clean it which would be bringing in our back up, the oven cleaner.
All you would simply do is apply the oven cleaner with the clamp open.
Actually you're going to want to, you can hold it or you can wedge something, maybe a pencil perhaps in between the clamp and the rod.
Then all you want to do is apply the oven cleaner all over, take a paper towel, wipe it off and then take a damp rag or ordinary towel and get off any of the excess that you missed with your paper towel.
So, there you have it, just a few tips on how to stay clean.